https://www.gemsys.ca/about-gem/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
By using or accessing this website you signify your acknowledgment and assent to the Privacy Policy below.
If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this website. GEM Systems, Inc. can revise this policy at any time by updating this Privacy Policy document, and your use after such change signifies that you accept the changed terms. Please check this document periodically for changes.
This document is designed to let you know how GEM Systems, Inc. collect, use and protect the information you provide on our website.
Personal Data
If you access GEM’s website, you do so on an anonymous basis and personal information is not required. Exceptions include signing up for a newsletter, requesting a quotation or sending us a question via email. Generally, we design data entry forms so that only the information for communicating with you is absolutely required; other data may be entered on an optional basis. We encourage you to provide optional data so that we may better understand and service your needs; however, we respect that the decision is yours as to whether to provide this information.
If you wish to update or delete personal information, we will endeavor to correct, update or remove the information provided. To request an update, please send an email to info@gemsystems.ca. We request that you entitle your message “Update Personal Information” so that we can make necessary changes quickly and efficiently.
Use of Personal Data
GEM Systems, Inc. does not rent, sell or otherwise distribute to third parties, your personal data when you enter it in a form on this site. We use all reasonable efforts to protect the confidentiality of your information, but we will have no liability for disclosure of any information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties. We also reserve the right to change or update the Privacy Policy documented here at any time, with reasonable notice to website users. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to www.gemsys.ca.
We may share statistical or aggregated non-personal information with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. The purpose is to customize our website content so that we provide information that is of value to our website visitors.
IP Tracking and Cookies
This website also may detect and use your IP address or domain name for internal traffic monitoring and capacity purposes or to otherwise administer www.gemsys.ca. We do not acquire any personal information – this information may be used to track traffic patterns to assist in improving site content and overall customer value. This site may use cookies for site administration purposes. You may disable this feature in your browser if required.
Other Scenarios
GEM Systems, Inc. reserves the right to disclose user information if there is reason to believe that disclosure is required to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be injuring or interfering with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other www.gemsys.ca users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.
Sites to Which We Link
This web site may contain links to third-party web sites. As these third-party sites are not under our control, we do not assume responsibility for the contents or privacy practices of any linked site or any link on a linked site.
Comments
We welcome any comments you may have regarding GEM’s website or the Privacy Policy contained here. Please send any comments to us via e-mail.
BACK
REQUEST A CALLBACK
If you would like to receive a callback from GEM Systems.
Name*
Phone*
Email*
Comments
Please select the Circle
and click the Submit button.
Submit
Please wait...
NEWS and EVENTS
GEOEXCE Article about GEM Systems Magnetometers
Mining Indaba, South Africa, February 3-6
GEM Systems Holiday Hours of Operation: Closed Dec 21 - Jan 2.
View All
REQUEST A QUOTE
Select your productOverhauser Mag
- GSM 19Proton Mag - GSM19TPotassium Mag - GSMP 35VLF EM - GSMVSystems - GSMP 35A(B)Potassium Mag - GSMP 35ABase Station Mag - GSM 19WLight Weight Mag - GSMP 35UAirbird - GSMP 35U(B)Monarch - GSMP 35 UTMonitoring Scalar Euromag - GSM 90Monitoring DIDD Vector
Mag - GSM 90F5DSuperGrad - GSMP 20S3Array
(
[6158] => Array
(
[title] => Ground
[0] => Array
(
[title] => Overhauser Mag
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/gsm-19-overhauser/
)
[1] => Array
(
[title] => Proton Mag - GSM19T
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/proton-precession-magnetometer-gradiometer/
)
[2] => Array
(
[title] => Potassium Mag - GSMP 35
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/potassium-magnetometer/
)
[3] => Array
(
[title] => VLF EM - GSMV
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/request-a-quote-for-vlf-em-3-frequency-system-or-vlf-em-2d-resistivity-software/
)
)
[title] => Systems - GSMP 35A(B)
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/potassium-airborne-magnetometer-gradiometer/
)
[5] => Array
(
[title] => Potassium Mag - GSMP 35A
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/potassium-airborne-magnetometer-gradiometer/
)
[6] => Array
(
[title] => Base Station Mag - GSM 19W
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/airborne-and-ground-base-station-magnetometer/
)
)
)
[8] => Array
(
[title] => Airbird - GSMP 35U(B)
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/uav-systems/
)
[9] => Array
(
[title] => Monarch - GSMP 35 UT
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/uav-systems/
)
)
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/scalar-magnetometer-gradiometer/
)
[11] => Array
(
[title] => Monitoring DIDD Vector
Mag - GSM 90F5D
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/didd-vector-magnetometer/
)
[12] => Array
(
[title] => SuperGrad - GSMP 20S3
[url] => https://www.gemsys.ca/quotations/supergrad/
)
)
)
Home|About GEM|GEM Technologies|Applications|Quotations|Resource Library|News|Contact Us|
Site Map
©2020 Gem Systems Advanced Magnetometers. All Rights Reserved.
